So now, may I call on for our next item,
Ms. Florence Dela Cruz?
For this item,
Florence will be cooking you a private dinner
in a set-up by the beach.
So, Ms. Florence...
Let's get this bidding started.
Private dinner cooked by Ms. Florence.
Anyone?
One million pesos.
And if you're thinking to outbid me,
don't try anymore.
Because I won't waste this chance
to be with an important person to me.
I won't waste the chance
to be with you again, Florence.
Florence!
And what went into your mind earlier?
Why did you make a bid?
Didn't you even think how Antonia would feel?
Antonia and I are over.
So you called it quits again,
and now, you're going after me?
What?
You'll use me again to make her jealous?
Is that it?
Nero, I don't want anymore.
I don't want to expect. I don't want to hope.
So please, don't play with my heart.
It's you who said that Florence is our cook,
and it's not good to see
that both Ferells are fighting because of her.
Sit together and talk.
Man-to-man, from one Ferell to another.
I don't care what others would say.
My God, dude, you're both Ferells.
Have you forgotten what Grandfather said?
That if we, Ferells, have a problem,
we fix it, together.
That's right. Just fix that problem.
The last thing we want
is us tearing each other apart
because of Florence.
Florence? What happened?
Is there a problem?
Florence is here.
The kid will spend the night here.
But don't worry, she's safe here,
away from your grandsons whose relationship
is a bit complicated with her.
Did Florence leave already?
Yes, Sir, she left already.
Well, call the recruitment agency.
- We need a cook now...
- Don Ferell...
Double their salary,
and talk to the best cooks.
Once they find out how big the salary is,
they'll agree to work for us.
Sir?
Yes?
Can I please speak freely?
And please listen.
She wants to say goodbye to you,
but you made orders not to disturb you,
that's why she didn't insist.
But before she went home,
she left you a message.
Hello, Grandfather Garp.
Ma'am Serafica said you're busy,
that's why I won't disturb you
and say goodbye.
But the reason why I'm doing this video
is to show you
how to cook your favorite chopsuey recipe!
But before we start, Grandfather Garp,
we need to do a magic ritual.
That's important.
Game.
Join me.
Did you do that?
Maybe you're thinking right now
that I'm a fool,
but that's the most important thing
before we start cooking,
so that our heart is ready to cook.
Because in cooking, the heart is important.
So after our ritual,
are you ready, Grandfather Garp?
Are you ready to cook your favorite chopsuey?
Yes, ready.
So first, Grandfather Garp,
we need to wash our hands
so our food will be clean.
There you go. Next, let's heat up our pan.
But our fire should be just moderate...
there, just like that.
And then, let's wait to have energy,
something like,
"Let's go, Florencia. Let's cook now".
That's it. So, let's just wait.
Game. It's now calling me, Grandfather Garp.
Now, if you can feel the energy
like what I'm feeling right now,
let's add some oil.
There you go.
Let's add onions and saute them.
And once this is okay,
let's put the snow peas,
everybody's favorite.
Then, add a little water,
and then, sesame oil.
And then, Grandfather Garp, once that's okay,
let's add my secret ingredient.
Here it is.
Are you ready, Grandfather Garp?
Grand reveal!
It's roasted chicken.
Just shred it into pieces
and mix it with what you are cooking.
Add a little salt and crushed pepper,
you now have chopsuey!
Thank you so much, Grandfather Garp.
I will never forget you
and all the people here.
You're the best grandfather that I've met.
Oh, Grandfather Garp,
don't post this on social media.
My real grandfather might see this
and feel bad about me.
That's all. Thank you.
Bye!
No wonder Florence is not
replying to my text messages.
And I was calling her
the whole morning earlier.
Should we go to her?
Let's talk to her, and let's ask her
if there's something we can help her with.
I don't think that's a good idea.
I agree.
It looks like her parents are not happy.
She didn't explain to her parents
that she was cooking for us.
They thought she was cooking for little kids.
Well, to be fair,
you guys act like toddlers sometimes, right?
Wow.
For real.
- We don't.
- Right?
So, what will happen to Florence?
Will she be okay?
Grandfather Garp said
that she can continue her studies.
After all, she's a scholar.
And the scholarship will be valid,
unless she has a failing mark
or she violated school rules
and got suspended.
But the bigger question is,
what will happen to Florence and Nero?
The last time I saw Florence...
she looked really heartbroken.
If you were given mixed signals
like what Nero did.
Right?
At the end of the day, Nero led Florence on.
Now, Florence is gone from his life...
for good.
That's sad.
So, what happens now?
That's enough.
Why do you have this?
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry... I didn't mean it.
It suddenly caught fire.
Believe me, Grandfather.
Even if I'm calm...
I don't want to see the face of this woman.
So please... Grandfather, throw her out.
Let's go, Florence.
She's my girlfriend.
Shall we, my... Chummy pie?
Let's share.
Okay, you can use the other side.
Your head is big.
Let's adjust.
Did I just offend you?
- Or not?
- Not really.
Just for tonight...
- Tomorrow...
- The sky is so beautiful.
Come on, let's look at it.
What? Game?
What?
What? Don't you even
have a perimeter defense?
What do you think?
[DNA Paternity Report]
[Florence Dela Cruz, Lorenzo Almero]
[Probability of Paternity: 99.999%]
Don Rogelio, you called for me?
Talk to our guys.
I want to know everything
about Florence Dela Cruz.
Everything about her.
How did she grow up?
Who are her parents she grew up with?
I want to know everything
about my grandchild.
So that I will be ready when she comes back.
Yes, Sir.
So, what's your plan?
Don't tell me that's it, bro.
You'll just let Florence be?
I've hurt her so much.
That's why maybe I'm the last person
she wants to see.
But we both know
you didn't do that to hurt her.
We know you were doing that to protect her.
I already talked to Antonia.
I know what she did.
Honestly, I was surprised.
It's so out of character of her,
but I guess she had her valid reasons.
That gives you a very valid reason as well.
You know, if Florence knows why you did it,
she'll understand.
If you can sacrifice to protect her,
then you should not give up on
trying to make her understand.
You did this not to hurt her,
but to protect her.
She's one of a kind, bro.
Don't give her up.
Or else, you'd regret this
for the rest of your life.
Good morning, Mother!
Good morning, Father!
Good morning, Florence.
What are you doing here?
Florence, he's been waiting here
for quite some time.
He said you owe him dinner,
because in the auction,
he bid a million pesos
for you to cook for him.
Is that true?
One million pesos.
And if any of you are thinking to outbid me,
don't try anymore.
Because I won't waste this chance
to be with an important person to me.
I won't waste the chance
to be with you again, Florence.
That's for charity.
It'll be a pity if I take back
the one million pesos
if Florence won't cook for me.
See? It's for charity.
Just grant his request
and think about all the people
that will benefit from that donation.
Well...
A deal is a deal,
so I'll honor what we've agreed upon.
So when, how, and where do you want
to have dinner, Mr. Ferell?
Actually, you don't have to cook for me.
I just want to talk to you.
Is this one of your favors?
No, but before, you asked me
for a minute to explain yourself.
That's what I'm going to ask from you.
A minute to explain myself.
So do you think
Nero will try to win her back?
I talked to him last night,
and I hope it's enough to push him.
This is exciting.
I hope they patch things up,
and I hope they'll end up together.
So there'll be a sequel to this story.
- Yeah.
- Sequel...
If they patch things up and end up together,
there's no more sequel.
Technically, the story is finished.
Troy has a point.
Exactly.
You talk as if Nero and Florence
are characters in a book.
Well, what's important now
is that they have a chance
to fix their relationship, right?
That's right! That's how one should think.
You're really the best, Lina.
Can I join you guys?
Oh guys, by the way, my treat.
Let's go to Paris again.
Why don't we go to Korea instead?
Oh my God, BTS...
We just went to Korea last year.
- Let's go to Paris.
- As in now.
Okay, one minute.
Go.
I like you.
I really like you.
And during the time we were still pretending,
what I was feeling for you, is true.
But...
Just a second.
Can I ask you a favor?
What is it?
Can Aylip stop bothering Florence Dela Cruz?
Break up with her.
Finish whatever it is that you have,
and let's get back together.
Do you think I want to reconcile with you?
Do you think that you have a choice, Nero?
You and I were meant to be together.
I can destroy her.
She lied in front of the school
when she agreed to be your girlfriend.
And I can make a case to the dean,
that's a violation of
the ethical standards of our school.
And the least that could happen is...
it could warrant a suspension.
And if I'm not mistaken,
that suspension could cancel her scholarship.
But I was wrong.
I thought I was protecting you,
but I was hurting you even more.
So I'll ask a favor from you,
so I can prove what I'm feeling.
- And everything...
- Okay, your one minute is over.
Time's up. You can stop now.
Florence...
didn't you even give him a grace period?
Let him finish.
Go ahead, just continue, you left me hanging.
I will do everything
to prove to you
that I deserve to be a part of your life.
Really?
Let's see how far you can go.
Hey, Joshua! That's hands-off.
You might seal the side mirror and tires.
This is safe with us.
- We'll take care of this.
- Keep an eye and do not steal.
- We'll take care of it.
- Hey, Ms. Marie, Ms. Rose.
- Florence.
Here it is.
Welcome to my world! This is my world.
It's a bit messy here,
and there are a lot of people.
Everyone knows each other,
like Mr. Dennis and Mr. Gilbert.
Hello.
Life here is simple, but fun.
So it's fun.
Yes, it's fun, but difficult.
And you can't be a weakling here.
Outfits like that is a no here.
You should be tough here.
So? Are you tough?
Yes, of course.
Hello, Ms. Diding.
It looks like
your galunggong fish is fresh today.
Go for galunggong.
We'll help you.
No need, Florence, I can handle this.
Ms. Diding, don't be shy.
My companion here is in top shape.
Nero can handle that.
What are you waiting for?
Go for the gold.
- No problem.
- Go for galunggong.
I can handle that.
That's light. I can carry that.
You should take this one.
Is that it?
Thank you, Nero.
Thank you, Florence.
Hey, your companion is handsome.
You're welcome.
Come on, let's go there.
Sir, can we still ride with you?
It's full already.
When is the next trip?
So this fool can experience
riding a public transportation.
It's a holiday today,
that's why the jeeps are taking tourists
to the falls.
But the other jeeps are probably
on their way.
Okay.
Let's not wait anymore, Florence.
We can sit up there.
- Is that okay?
- Of course.
Just be careful.
Let's go?
Sure.
You can handle that.
Be careful.
Here, hold on to this.
Cool?
Mister, let's go.
They hate me, don't they?
They have a reason to hate you.
You hurt their friend.
The things you do for love.
So, how's your heart?
Well, I thought letting go
would be difficult,
but the truth is...
I seem to be coping pretty well.
That's good.
You act like I'm the only broken-hearted one.
What about you?
Well, there are two ways to react
when you know the person
you love likes someone else.
You can be magnanimous and be happy for her,
which I did.
Or you can be an Antonia, and blackmail him.
Good one.
I can't believe that girl.
The audacity to show herself to us
after what she did to Florence.
Camille, in situations like this,
just think WWFD.
WWFD?
What would Florence do?
I'm sure Florence will forgive her.
Actually, I'm sure she has forgiven Antonia.
If that's the case,
then let's all be like Florence.
Let's open our hearts
and learn to forgive, right?
I still don't like her.
I mean, look...
she's using her charms again to trap Owen.
I'll be honest with you, Antonia.
I really appreciate your capacity to love.
I thought Antonia was all about reputation,
but I was wrong.
There's more to you than meets the eye,
and that's your heart.
We're the same.
Lina, girl.
Why don't you keep an eye on Owen?
I think you two will be perfect together.
I agree.
We'll set you up with him.
Troy will help us.
Yeah.
Troy, help us set Lina up with Owen.
Sure.
Yippee!
Oh well... For us with a heart that loves...
but is unlucky in love.
I think you should
just say sorry to them as well.
Hey.
"Oh, hey"?
That's all you can say, "oh, hey"?
Did I say something wrong?
It seems you're so dense
about what's happening.
What are you talking about?
What I'm saying is,
do you agree to set me up with Owen?
Why? Is it bad?
Is it prohibited?
We don't have a relationship.
You're right.
Maybe I should be dating someone else,
since we don't have a relationship, right?
Now, get some mangoes,
so we'll have something for dessert later.
Okay, which one?
This one?
No, that's not good. It has patches.
Get the other one.
This one?
No, not that one.
The other one, that one.
- That one.
- This one?
- That's it.
- Are you sure?
Nero!
Ouch...
Hey, are you okay?
- Wait.
- Hey!
- No, don't. Please.
Hey, let's step down here first.
Let it rest first.
- Let's stop for a while.
- I think I sprained my ankle.
- Let's stop first.
- Don't worry, I'm okay.
No, we won't walk first. Just stay there.
Ouch.
Why did you force yourself to get it
when you can't do it?
You said that was delicious.
I will do everything for you.
So I can give you what you want.
Are you okay now?
Nero, I don't think it's just a sprain.
It's like something cracked.
- Ouch!
- Can you walk?
I can... just wait.
We need to get out of here.
Ouch.
Hey! Let's go.
- We're getting soaked already.
- Wait...
Ouch, wait.
Wait...
Wait!
Hey! Hurry.
Just go slowly. Don't force it.
Ouch.
Ouch!
- Slowly.
- Just a little more.
Slowly.
Just a little more.
- Ouch.
- Just a little more.
Don't get your head wet.
Just a little more. Come on.
Just stay there.
What are you doing?
I'm sharing my thermal energy with you
so you won't feel cold and have difficulties.
Just like what I watch on TV.
Hi, you're so pretty.
Oh, that looks so good... so good.
What are you doing here?
I just wanted to say that I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
I've been really selfish lately,
and I've hurt Florence.
I have no excuse for my behavior.
It was... I was just really being immature.
Shouldn't you be apologizing to Florence.
Right?
After all, you've hurt her.
That was my intention,
but when Owen said that you guys are here,
I assumed that she was here too,
but you're right.
I should be on my way
to apologize to Florence personally.
It's not a good idea.
Why not?
She should apologize to Florence.
Owen meant, maybe it's the wrong timing
to go to Florence.
Maybe she's busy.
I think more accurately, they're both busy.
So Nero is with her right now?
Yes.
Oh my gosh.
I knew it.
Like I'm just thinking about it now,
I'm so thrilled.
Oh my God.
Well, maybe they're very sweet now.
Like, they are ants
because they're super sweet.
Probably, they're holding hands now
while walking.
And then, catching each other's gaze,
and it's like there's this invisible force
that's drawing them closer together.
Close enough for a kiss.
A true love's kiss.
I thought you were planning something evil.
Ouch.
Nero Sebastian Araneta Ferell,
you have the nerve to accuse me of that.
- Whatever, you're on your own.
- Ouch, that hurts!
Hey, wait...
- What's with you?
- Ouch.
Will you really neglect me?
Can't you see I can't walk?
Me? Neglecting you?
So now you're saying I'm neglecting you
when I was so concerned about you earlier,
and now you're thinking ill of me?
Why do you get mad easily?
Why do I get mad easily?
Maybe you've forgotten,
in this part of the story,
you're the one who wronged me.
You shouldn't be joking because
you have no right to joke around.
Ouch.
As for me, I would never buy that pretension
to become boyfriend and girlfriend first.
I mean, it could cause
a lot of complications, right?
With... you know what happened
with Florence and Nero.
They were just pretending
until it became real.
Well, that's why, there's a saying, right?
You can get lost,
but sooner or later,
you'll find your way back into love.
It's so corny.
- Oh...
- Tell me that again, Aldus,
once you've fallen in love with me.
But be careful, guys.
Even if you do find your way to love,
you can still get lost... just like me.
Yeah, spoken like a true villain
of the story.
All right, Camille.
- Yeah.
- But that is fair.
I do deserve that.
You do.
Are you two okay?
Yeah.
Why did you suddenly become quiet?
Yes.
Don't tell me you're just like Mark,
who's always quiet.
Where is your energy?
I'm going home.
Are you going with me
or you'll be staying behind?
You know what, we better leave.
Yeah, we better do that.
Sorry, boys, we'll go ahead.
- See you later.
- Bye.
Bye.
Wait... did I say a bad joke?
I don't think it was you, Tristan.
Maybe there's something going on
between Lina and Troy?
Is Antonia right?
Something is going on between you and Lina?
Bro... where are you going?
Let's go.
What's happening?
Did I do something wrong?
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
That's where you're good at,
always apologizing.
"Sorry, Florence. I was just joking."
"Sorry, Florence. I didn't mean it."
"Sorry, Florence. I was just protecting you."
"Sorry, Florence, for breaking your heart."
Right? You keep on saying sorry.
To tell you the truth,
I'm already scared to open my heart again.
Because I don't want to hear you saying sorry
because you've hurt me again!
That's always been my problem.
I've been raised to read people well.
But it does come in handy for people like us,
who exist in a world where people
can create their own terrible agendas.
Grandfather Garp shielded us from that.
That's why we're all together in the mansion
and not with our parents,
so we don't get involved with the intricacies
of our family business.
I admire your grandfather.
He really does take care of you guys.
What I can say is that I want that too.
Don't feel bad.
As you've said,
being able to read people
can come in as handy.
Think of it this way,
some of the mutants have powers
to read people's minds.
That's so cool, right?
So cool.
Just like what Uncle Ben said,
it can also be a curse.
You know...
before Nero even realized
that he liked Florence...
I already saw it in his eyes.
And I wanted him to look at me
the same way that he looked at her.
And recap to last week's episode,
fate made me realize
that you can't force love.
Maybe if there's something
that fate taught me,
it's that we really have to give
our best shot when it comes to love.
So is that our mantra?
To give it our best
and expect nothing in return?
Not really, maybe what's more appropriate is,
we give it our best,
and hope that someone will return the favor.
Keep hoping, keep believing.
And someday...
someone will come along
who will love us honestly and truthfully.
You really have a way with your words, Owen.
I'm surprised Florence didn't fall for you,
because if I were her...
I would've fallen for your sweet words.
It would've been so easy for me
to fall in love with you.
I mean... no, that's not what I mean.
I'm not implying that I will fall for you.
Ouch.
No, I'll really fall for you.
Really?
You know, I probably should go.
It was really nice seeing you.
I'll see you later.
Hey!
Nero Sebastian Araneta Ferell,
are you really going to leave
as if nothing happened?
What?
You're leaving, that's just about it?
I'm pissed whenever I see you.
Do you know why?
Because I remember what you did to me.
But it doesn't mean
that I don't want to see you anymore.
It doesn't mean
that you shouldn't show yourself and leave.
And that doesn't mean...
that all my feelings for you
will just go away.
What?